[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Thursday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "White House"], "PERSON": ["Obama", "Obama"]}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", ":", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Let me start with you Brianna, what is going on down where you are and will there be any re-election tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "No, really at the White House, we're not expecting to see President Obama and the action very much is on the senate where allies (ph) are at the White House at this point, President Obama said today he does believe that the shutdown will be over by Thursday.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brianna"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "And in terms of both, which may actually lead to a real deal, what is the process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, there are potential scenarios which I won't get into because it will probably make your head spin in the senate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Is this likely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, it's hard to say at this point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "What is your view of his behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, I think that one of the things we all should do right now is not talk about personality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 73, "question": "At what point is the out right selfish, self-interest of Ted Cruz and his colleagues outweigh the American interest in the global economic interest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "There again, I think that we don't do is talk about personalities ...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Are you prepared to see that risk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "... as a Party to avoid that?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "I continue to work with other republicans in the House to see if we can find a resolution to this issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim Himes", "Marsha Blackburn"]}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "JJ", "EX", ":", "NN", ":", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "So, even if the president were in -- you know, if the president had any ability to control the republicans and the House of Representatives, which by the way, the Speaker of the House does not have as evidence by the failure of his idea today even if the president could control the House of Representatives, what would you be negotiating on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNPS", ",", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNPS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "A little later there (ph), Jim Himes and Marsha Blackburn, thank you both very much indeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House of Representatives", "House", "House of Representatives"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.S. Treasury"]}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "What happens to money in America and around the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Nothing immediately unless there's delay in payment by the U.S. Treasury.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "WDT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "How does that factor rate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Look, let me tell you the first part of that question is what happens if they don't raise the debt ceiling and the U.S. is in this case where Richard was talking about, we're trying to pick and choose which bills to pay that would be really terrible for your 401K, it would be terrible for stock.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "It's very simple Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", ",", "RB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "You study these markets around the world but almost anybody I know, at what point do they start to really tank (ph) and at what point does it become almost inevitable that massive financial damage will be done regardless of whether they reach any kind of law second settlement?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", ":", "NN", ":", "CC", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "So, on the second issue, Piers, damage has been done, has been done to the real economy, people are spending less, companies are hiring less, so that's a real problem because it's not like our economy was growing very fast to begin with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Is all this just going to kill that, but also we're heading back to a potential risk of recession again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Look, it is kind of productive at best.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "What is your gut feeling about how bad this is going to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I'm worried about the complacency.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, let me start with you because this is fascinating, do you taught Ted Cruz at Harvard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well I'm not sure how much I taught him but I sat in the front of the class while he was in the class raising his hand, always his right hand making very intelligent points and really winning debates all the time in the class including winning debates with his professors.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Harvard"], "PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz", "Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "One of the best students you've had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "One of the sharpest students I had.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What do you think his strategy is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I think he deeply believes what he's doing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "When he is basically taking an established law like ObamaCare, whether you like possibly don't know or even know a thing and using that as a stick to shut down the American government, that's taking you a bit far, isn't it principle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Not only that I think it really raises very serious constitutional questions of the kind that Ted Cruz should be interested in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "What is the problem and from all your experience and is detailed in your book, how do we get through this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, I had suggested a mediator but it's too late now we're on the brink of a major decision, a catastrophic decision that we don't take action.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ".", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Is that great leadership?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Well, if you look at the record, Piers, the president has called the leadership then (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "I mean, is this split between a newly galvanized Tea Party on the main body politic of the GOP, going to be a very much of problem form (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "It's going to be a problem form (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["74 percent"]}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CD", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Would you like to see most members of congress reelect next election among rich (ph) voters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "No. 74 percent ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "-NONE-", "NN", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Did you imagine him actually making a serious run for presidency?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I think he's heard (ph) his chances of doing that because to get to be the president it's not enough to win some primaries.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]